const questionsData=[{
    question:"The Right against exploitation is a ____ ?",
    options:["Constitutional Right","Method","Fundamental Right","Legal Right "],
    correctAns:"Fundamental Right"
},{
    question:"A (n) ________ appearing on a web page opens another document when clicked ?",
    options:["anchor","URL", "hyperlink","reference"],
    correctAns:"hyperlink"
},{
    question:"Which of the following writs provides a remedy for a person who has been unlawfully held in prison ?",
    options:["Certiorari ","Habeas Corpus","Mandamus","Prohibition"],
    correctAns:"Habeas Corpus"
},{
    question:"Which of the following functions is not performed by servers ?",
    options:["Email processing","Database sharing","Processing Websites","Word processing"],
    correctAns:"Word processing"
},{
    question:"Which among the following is synonymous to 'Flourish' ?",
    options:["Wither","Languish","Thrive","Shrivel"],
    correctAns:"Thrive"
},{
    question:"Mark the correct antonym of 'Enigma'.",
    options:["Mystery","Charade","Make-believe","Clarity"],
    correctAns:"Clarity"
},{
    question:"The idea of residual powers in Indian constitution has been taken from the constitution of:",
    options:["Canada","South Africa","Japan","USA"],
    correctAns:"Canada"
},{
    question:"Select the set of numbers that is similar to the following set: (11,16,31)?",
    options:["(17,22,37)","(29,34,41)","(19,24,31)","(23,28,31)"],
    correctAns:"(17,22,37)"
},{
    question:"\"Bird\" is related to \"Wings\" in the same way as \"Fish\" is related to \"_______\" ?",
    options:["Belly","Scales","Fins","Gills"],
    correctAns:"Fins"
},{
    question:"What is the meaning of idiom \"Carry a chip on one's shoulder\" ?",
    options:["Entertaining a grudge over a past event","Moving daintily across rooms","Having a plate inserted to fix the collar bone","Carrying multiple stars over the lapel"],
    correctAns:"Entertaining a grudge over a past event"
}]

export default questionsData;